Hello!
Its time to party.
Now we're going to discuss the appropriate games for the birthday party.
For example, if you're having a party for a 5 year old, you want to choose games that are lively.
Invite a clown, have face painting.
Have games that are going to make the children, and when they leave they'll be glad that they came to the birthday party.
You might even want to purchase party favors, things that would allow them just to be really excited about the game.
If you are having a birthday party for someone that's close to teen age, you will like to choose games that will make them think, but also make them have fun as well.
Don't forget about adults.
Adults love to play in birthday parties.
Come on, who likes to come to a birthday party and just sit around and talk to people that you may or may not know.
Get everyone involved.
Choose a game that incorporates everyone.
For example, if who ever the birthday party is for, make a story about that person.
That person like to eat at McDonald's or Burger King or a restaurant.
Make the story flow to where people part of the party will be able to choose or guess their favorite item or things.
Don't forget to consider your audience.
Make sure that they would enjoy games that are lively, and most importantly, have fun.